

## **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Germany, Traunstein (Bayern) Citizenship: Ukrainian +49 160 914 297 49 seletskaya.kira@gmail.com

**LinkedIn** Github Portfolio

## **SUMMARY**

I worked in sales for more than 15 years. But due to recent events, I left my country. I was faced with the question: continue my career or start a new one, I chose the latter. In my previous career as a sales specialist, I achieved the following accomplishments:

- won the title of most productive manager.
- brought in and managed the largest deal in the history of the company.
- my department was named the most successful department, with the highest profit margin repeatedly.
- had the lowest staff turnover within my department, reducing the rate from 30% annually to 10%

But the time came to make a new choice, and I chose IT

## **TECHNICAL STACK**

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React
- MobX, Redux, Redux-toolkit
- OOP
- GIT, GitHub,
- HTML5, CSS/SASS

and ready for new chalanges

#### Basic knowledge:

 Java, QA, Linux, RTK-Query, SQL, NoSQL and MongoDB, Algorithms, Project management

# **SELETSKA KIRA**

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Frontend Developer**

InternShip 08.2023 - 12.2023

Main tasks: transfer a board game online, create a website for a web designer. Our work was carried out in a team of three frontend developers under the guidance of a frontend architect. Tasks were assigned to the team or to each employee separately. Basic communication via GitHub.

# **Board game "Space Expatriate"**



The game for two or three and more players. Has five decks and additional game cards. The program was written in VScode, library React, language TypeScript, state manager MobX, styles SASS, with using OOP. The game is saved and restored by ID in local storage.

The rules and a detailed description of the game can be found here

#### Portfolio website for UI/UX designer



The website was written in VScode,

library React, language TypeScript, styles SASS, with using Figma.

## **Career break**

06.2022 - 08.2023

Moved from Ukraine to Germany. Completed training to become a web developer

#### **Head of Sales Department**

Kyiv, Ukraine SILVEX 925 Direction B2B, B2C 01.2022 - 06.2022

Jewelry, sale throughout Ukraine (wholesale, retail, B2C and B2B call centers, TV sales).

Main task: managing the sales direction.

Responsibilities: strategy review, increasing KPI, script writing, writing a company's working manual (interaction algorithms within the company and company-client), recruiting staff members.

## **Head of Sales**

Kyiv, Ukraine KSG Direction B2B 02.2021 - 09.2021

Commercial real estate for rent, 28 locations in Kyiv.

Main task: managing commercial real estate. Additional tasks - creating a call center to consolidate four projects.

Responsibilities: creating an alternative sales department from scratch, producing KPI, producing a new department development strategy, following the plan to lease the office spaces

FRONTEND DEVELOPER SELETSKA KIRA

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Fontend Developer**

Germany, Berlin Starta Institute by Tel-Ran 11.2022 - 08.2023 JavaScript, SASS, React, Redux, Reduxtoolkit, RTK-Query, SQL, noSQL and MongoDB, Algorithms, Project Management Basic

Java, QA, Linux Additional

TypeScript, MobX

## **Diploma Project**

Online Store (JavaScript, React, Redux, Redux-toolkit, HTML, CSS/SASS, GitHub) Source link <u>Store</u>

#### **Finance**

Ukraine, Sumy Sumy National Agrarian University 09.2004 - 07.2008 Majoring in Finance Bachelor's degree in Economics

## **LANGUAGES**

- English Intermediate (in progress)
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

#### **Head of Sales/Commercial Director**

Kyiv, Ukraine Vista Project (Construction) Direction B2B 09.2018 - 09.2020

Repair and construction works.

Main task: establishing a department from scratch. Contracts ranging from one month to one year.

Responsibilities: creating a departmental workflow system, developing KPIs and sales funnels, developing a manager's action algorithm from the first cold call to receiving a recommendation letter; recruiting, adapting, training, and motivating employees, achieving sales targets.

## **Call Center Supervisor**

Kyiv, Ukraine NOVBUD (Construction) Direction B2B, B2C 06.2017 - 09.2018

Sale of real estate from the developer, managing 3 residential complexes.

Supervised up to 24 managers.

Main tasks: recruiting and training managers, achieving sales targets, scriptwriting, developing new sales strategies, conducting training sessions, monitoring managers' performance.

Joined the company as a call center operator. After 3 months of work, was promoted to a supervisor based on an internal competition.

### **Sales Department Manager**

Kyiv, Ukraine RE Expert (Real Estate) Direction B2C 05.2012 - 04.2015

Services for the purchase and sale of primary and secondary real estate.

Joined the company as a sales manager.

After a year of work (since 2013), was promoted to Sales Department Manager.

#### **Sales Manager**

Kyiv, Ukraine Snack Production (FMCG) Direction B2B, B2C 06.2011 - 03.2012

Increasing sales in the assigned territory, attracting new customers, controlling accounts receivable.

#### Sales Manager

Romny-Konotop, Ukraine Private Enterprise Dalniye Ostrova (FMCG) Direction B2B, B2C 03.2009 - 01.2011

Joined the company as a Sales Manager in Romny. After a year, participated in the opening of a branch in Konotop (since 2010), where the responsibilities of a Sales Manager were expanded to include those of a Branch Manager.